tradeboss.com 2019-07-26

# B2B Marketplace TradeBoss.com - Import Export, Business to Business Portal, FREE Business Website, Suppliers B2B Directory

**TradeBoss.com - Privacy Policy**

Last Update: 2018-05-24

**REGISTRATION**  
If you register on TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network as a member, we collect and store all the information you enter. Our Membership Statistics, Industrial and Geographical classification statistics are derived from these information. This information may be used to target our registered members for new services and promotions. Your e-mail address may be used by TradeBoss.com, TradeHolding.com B2B Network and certain members to contact you regarding new services and products in which you may be interested.  
We also display certain information you enter on your specific company detail page including but not limited to: your company name, your first name and lastname and your job title.

**REGISTRATION OBLIGATIONS**  
If you register in TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network, you agree to:  
(a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself and the company you represent  
(b) provide your e-mail address, postal address, phone, fax, website address (url) ONLY on site sections and fields where we specifically ask for these details  
(c) maintain and promptly update the Registration Content to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete and TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network reserves the right to suspend or terminate your member service.  
You understand that TradeBoss.com is a partner of TradeHolding.com, a global B2B network and your company information and any other publicly available information you provide on TradeBoss.com (including but not limited to: your company name, your first name and lastname and your job title) may appear on other TradeHolding.com partner sites.  
Your TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network Account Information and Member Profile are password-protected so that other TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network members and / or third parties will not have the ability to access, edit or delete this personal information. Any password protection system may be vulnerable to certain attacks, and therefore TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network cannot 100% guarantee the protection of your personal information from malicious third parties. We recommend you to do not disclose your password to anyone and change your password from time to time.

**PUBLISHING INFORMATION**  
Company Description, Trade Lead Publishing and Product Detail Publishing:  
All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network and therefore accessible by visitors, certain robots and members. The publicly available information can be also cached by search engines and robots and -as we do have no control over these entities- we can not influence the way these details are presented on certain pages / sites / etc. If you ever request your pages to be removed from our sites and servers we will do this but it is your responsibilitry to remove the publicly available information from any third party.  
Any Publishing Information that you use on TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network forms becomes public information and you respond for them (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights).  
If you submit any information to TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network to be published on our B2B Network through the publishing forms you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information.

**COOKIES**  
TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network uses cookies to maintain your information as you move throughout this site and facilitate your member activities. A cookie is a small piece of information used to identify an individual when the person is accessing a site. Cookies are used only for the intended purpose and scope of TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network.  
Cookies and the tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to this site, and understanding how visitors use this site. Cookies can also help customize this site for visitors. If you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. This site or the advertisers on this site may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process.  
If you want to block the use and saving of cookies from the Site on to their computers hard drive, you should take the necessary steps within your web browserâ€™s settings to block all cookies from the Site. Please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, certain parts of our Site may not function correctly. For information on how to disable cookies, refer to your browserâ€™s documentation.

**YOUR PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT AND USE**  
We may process your registration data ("registration data"). Registration data may include your email address and eventually your username. The source of this data is you. Registration data is required in order for you to be able to use the service. The legal bases for this processing are consent and the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.

We may process your account data ("account data"). Account data may include your full name, email address, country, city, address, phone number, company name, your position in the company, company registration number and fiscal numbers, company details, product details and trade lead details. The source of this data is you. The account data may be processed for the purposes of providing our services, communicating with you and allowing other members to contact you and send business leads for you (leads that you might be interested in or not). Certain account data (your name, your company name, your position in the company, your product details, your trade leads) is disclosed publicly on our website and other websites. Other account data (such as contact information, e-mail address, phone number) is disclosed privately to certain members upon request and type of membership. The legal bases for this processing are  
\- consent  
\- our legitimate interests, namely the operation of our business model.

We store your information primarily within our servers located in the USA and the European Economic Area. However, some features and requirements of our service, may involve transferring your information to third-party service providers outside the European Economic Area. When we do similar transfers, the transfers will be covered by the standard data protection clauses adopted by the European Commission or by another appropriate safeguard mechanism such as the Privacy Shield Framework.

**RETAINING AND DELETING PERSONAL DATA**

We will retain your Personal Data for as long as long as you maintain an account or subscription agreement or as otherwise necessary to provide you the Services. We will also retain your Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  
Users may request the deletion of their account by contacting us.  
We will retain and delete your personal data as follows:

We will delete all personal data 30 days after the approval of your account deletion request.  
Your communication data with other members will be deleted 5 years after you delete your account.

Notwithstanding the other provisions, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

**LOG DATA**

When you use the Services, our servers may automatically collect and store information, including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This log data may include, but is not limited to, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the address of the web page you visited before using the Services, the operating system you are using, the date and time of your accessing the Services, geolocation information, type of device, cookie data, and browser signatures.

Use of the Site and Services signifies consent to our use of cookies, including and without limitation Third Party cookies that we may choose to use for analytics or other purposes. You agree that should you disable cookies on your browser, certain aspects of the Services may be unavailable to you, and that we are not responsible for any adverse effects arising from your browser or other computer or mobile settings.

You agree that you are responsible for adhering to all laws, policies, and other regulations in your relevant jurisdiction(s), including but not limited to all laws requiring that cookie use must be disclosed. We disclaim all liability in this area.

**INFORMATION DISCLOSURE**  
TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network does not disclose the collected information (except the Publishing Information) to any third parties, unless acting under the belief that such action is necessary to:  
(a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process  
(b) protect and defend the rights or property of TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network  
(c) act to protect the interests of its members or others.  
We reserve the right to disclose any collected information to authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network, our members, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.  
We reserve the right to disclose any collected information in response to a judicial order or when we believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.

TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network considers and respects an individual's privacy seriously and importantly. The services we provide require that we collect, process, use, display and distribute certain details you provide us. Therefore, TradeBoss.com and TradeHolding.com B2B Network does not guarantee that your information will be protected from exposure in any particular party or group. If you would like to remove your Company please Contact Us.

We welcome your additional input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

The data controller responsible for your personal data for is TradeHolding SRL, a Romania limited liability company; address 37, V. Lucaciu street, Satu Mare, Romania. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, your rights and/or our data collection practices, please contact our customer support.
